hclinfosystems.in 2019-06-30

# Privacy Policy - HCL Infosystems

HCL INFOSYSTEMSLIMITED (“HCL INFOSYSTEMS”) has created this statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for website. We do not link IP address to anything personally identifiable, which means that a user’s session can be tracked, but the user’s identity will remain anonymous. Our website may require you to give us contact information like your name, email address etc., while filling in certain forms. In such an event, we may use this contact information from the forms to send you relevant communication as required by the nature of that form/registration (e.g.,) By registering for an event, the user may receive communication specific to that event, by submitting a query / request for service, the user will get a response on the email / phone number from the concerned HCL INFOSYSTEMS personnel.We also use several web technologies like ‘cookies’ to gather visitor information and preferences to help provide our audience a better user experience.

However, it is possible that we may need to disclose personal information when required by law. We will disclose such information wherein we have a good-faith belief that it is necessary to comply with a court order, ongoing judicial proceeding, or other legal process served on us or to exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

Also, this site contains links to other sites. HCL INFOSYSTEMS is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

**Security**  
This website has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and/or alteration of information under our control. The data resides behind a firewall, with access restricted only to authorized HCL INFOSYSTEMS personnel.

**Non-disclosure of Personal Data**  
We will not sell, share, or otherwise distribute your Personal Data to third parties nor will we send you unsolicited email. Personal Data collected from you may also be transferred to a third party in the event that the business of this site or a part of it and the customer data connected with it is sold, assigned or transferred, in which case we would require the buyer, assignee or transferee to treat Personal Data in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Also, Personal Data may be disclosed to a third party if we are required to do so because of an applicable law, court order or governmental regulation, or if such disclosure is otherwise necessary in support of any criminal or other legal investigation or proceeding here or abroad.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your computer as a tag that identifies your computer. While cookies are often only used to measure website usage and effectiveness and to allow for ease of navigation or use and as such, are not associated with any personal information, they are also used at times to personalise a known visitor’s experience to a website by being associated with profile information or user preferences. To know more about cookies, please visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/), [www.youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/) and [en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie/)

Type of cookies used in HCL Infosystems.com

**Strictly necessary cookies**  
These cookies are strictly necessary to enable you to move about the site or to provide certain features you have requested. For example, access to restricted areas of the site where authentication is necessary. We consider following cookies are strictly necessary cookies: a) Session Cookie – A unique identifier given to each registered user, used to recognize them through their visit and when they return to the site b) No Cache Cookie – We cache our pages to improve the performance of our website. This cookie is set if a page need to bypass the cache and deliver a fresh content.

**Functionality cookies**  
These cookies enhance the functionality of website by storing your preferences. We consider following cookies as functionality cookies – a) Form Preference Cookies – Web Forms on our website is pre-populated with your data if you have already filled a similar form on our website in the past b)Content personalization cookies – We may store your geographic location and your selection from our list of personas to be able to provide a customized representation of our website content to suit your persona or geography.

**Performance Cookies**  
We use performance cookies across the website to help us provide our users with a better site experience. Information supplied by cookies helps us in understanding how our visitors use our website and this helps improve how we present our content to our visitors. We generally use user independent measurement and research tools to achieve this and when this is the case, these cookies may be set by a third party tool.

**Third party cookies**  
We embed videos from our official YouTube Channel. This may set cookies on your computer. Similarly, when you use some of the social share features, a cookie may be set by the widget to share content through. We do not control these cookies, you can check the relevant third party website for more information about these cookies. b) Our site is using display advertising functionality of Google Analytics which is used for remarketing feature to advertise online. To show advertisements, our site and Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on visitor’s past visits to our website.  
By using this site you agree that we can place cookies on your device.

**How to reject or delete cookies**  
You can set your browser in most instances to notify you before you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it or reject it. You can also generally set your browser to turn off cookies. Since cookies allow you to take advantage of some of our websites’ features, we recommend that you leave them turned on.

**Contacting the website admin**  
For questions regarding the privacy statement, practices of the website, or any other transaction issue, please fill the contact form.
